<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Help on</title><link>https://sprintobot.com/docs/help/</link><description>Recent content in Help on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:40:56 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sprintobot.com/docs/help/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview of Help</title><link>https://sprintobot.com/docs/overview-of-help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sprintobot.com/docs/overview-of-help/</guid><description>Write with your friends! Run a sprint and compete with your writing group! Focus on your writing, share word counts, write the most you can!
Getting Started #
Invite Sprinto to your server, then Set up Sprinto (or just start sprinting) Sprinting #
Sprint (basics) — common ways to use /sprint Sprint (all options) — complete sprint options guide During the sprint — join, leave, cancel, and setting your word count Sprint (admin) — the few sprint options and commands only available to Sprint MCs Help #
Overview of Help — this page Active Sprinter role — Setting up a role on your server named @Active Sprinters Admin commands — about the Admin
To use this command you must have the @SprintAdmin role, be an administrator on the server, or be the server owner.</description></item><item><title>Active Sprinter role</title><link>https://sprintobot.com/docs/active-sprinter-role/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sprintobot.com/docs/active-sprinter-role/</guid><description>What is the &amp;lsquo;Active Sprinter&amp;rsquo; role? #
In brief:
Makes members who are currently in a sprint with Sprinto more visible in the discord members list. It&amp;rsquo;s just an optional nice thing to make it more obvious when a sprint is running on your server. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why this documentation got so long for a simple feature. The @Active Sprinters role is an extra thing admins can set up, but is not necessary for the running of Sprinto.</description></item><item><title>Admin commands</title><link>https://sprintobot.com/docs/admin-commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sprintobot.com/docs/admin-commands/</guid><description>Commands available to guild owners, administrators and people with a role named SprintAdmin. Some commands are also available to people with a SprintMC role.
Sprint Admin intro #
A Sprint Admin [
Admin
To use this command you must have the @SprintAdmin role, be an administrator on the server, or be the server owner.
] is someone with extra privileges on a server. A server&amp;rsquo;s owner, its administrators, and anyone with a role named Sprint Admin.</description></item><item><title>Allowed channels (admin)</title><link>https://sprintobot.com/docs/allowed-channels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sprintobot.com/docs/allowed-channels/</guid><description>Sprinting channel whitelist (Sprinto Setup) #
If any channels on your server are set as &amp;lsquo;allowed&amp;rsquo; with set-allowed-channel then starting sprints will be disallowed in channels which have not been set as allowed. When a member of your server tries to sprint in a channel which has not been allowed they&amp;rsquo;ll pointed to all allowed channels. If no channels are explicitly set as &amp;lsquo;allowed&amp;rsquo; (the default) then Sprinto allows sprinting in all channels.</description></item><item><title>Carl-bot x Sprinto</title><link>https://sprintobot.com/docs/carl-bot-x-sprinto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sprintobot.com/docs/carl-bot-x-sprinto/</guid><description>Scheduling Sprints #
NOTE: Carl-bot is not associated with Sprinto. I&amp;rsquo;ve provided this info to help you schedule sprints, to extend Sprinto&amp;rsquo;s functionality beyond what it was originally designed for.
Want to scheduling sprints more than an hour in advance, or set up multiple sprints in a row? You can use Carl-bot for this purpose. Sprinto may get a built-in way in future, but for now there&amp;rsquo;s Carl-bot, a popular Discord bot which is developed completely independently of Sprinto (I have nothing to do with it!</description></item><item><title>Curious commands</title><link>https://sprintobot.com/docs/curious-commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sprintobot.com/docs/curious-commands/</guid><description>These commands are documented here mostly for curiousity&amp;rsquo;s sake. You don&amp;rsquo;t need any of them, and they&amp;rsquo;re largely not useful, but they&amp;rsquo;re documented here all the same.
parse #
@Sprinto#2517 parse time
Try parsing time with Sprinto&amp;rsquo;s time span parser.
Example: @Sprinto#2517 parse 3,000,000 seconds
Sprinto parses this as 34:17:20:00 or 34 days, 17 hours, 20 minutes
more examples
@Sprinto#2517 parse 1 day 3,000,000 seconds
Sprinto parses this as `35:17:20:00` or 35 days, 17 hours, 20 minutes See pengowray/TimeSpanParser on github for more about the open source TimeSpanParser library created by Pengo Wray for Sprinto.</description></item><item><title>Emoji Pets</title><link>https://sprintobot.com/docs/emoji-pets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sprintobot.com/docs/emoji-pets/</guid><description>Emoji Pet #
Your very own emoji pet is available as a reward to Sprinto Patreons and Ko-fi supporters.
Your emoji pet will keep you company on sprints and stop you from ever coming last 🙂
As of November 2023, all Sprinto Patreons ($2 tier and above) and all Ko-fi supporters will receive an emoji pet for November. If you&amp;rsquo;re a Patreon or Ko-fi supporter and don&amp;rsquo;t have an emoji pet, please let me know.</description></item><item><title>Emoji Pets TOS</title><link>https://sprintobot.com/docs/emoji-pets-tos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sprintobot.com/docs/emoji-pets-tos/</guid><description>Disclaimer / Terms of Service #
Virtual items (Emoji Pets and Pixel Pets) are a reward for Sprinto supporters, as a thank you for supporting the development, hosting and maintenance of Sprinto bot. They are not goods. They do not have value. They cannot be refunded. They cannot be traded and as such are neither fungible nor non-fungible. I reserve the right to remove your pet, or all pets, for any reason, including but not limited to because you&amp;rsquo;ve been disruptive, abusive of the bot, or because of factors like because Discord changes the API again and I can&amp;rsquo;t be bothered putting the effort in to keep up with it this time, or because I accidently messed up the database and lost your pet, or just because it all becomes too much for me.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://sprintobot.com/docs/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sprintobot.com/docs/faq/</guid><description>Sprinto isn&amp;rsquo;t responding to my commands #
Discord&amp;rsquo;s slash commands can be terribly inconsistent, and it can be hard to know if the problem is a permissions problem, or a discord UI/UX issue, or something else. I&amp;rsquo;ve written up a trouble shooting guide here that attempts to cover most of them:
https://www.patreon.com/posts/71439355
I&amp;rsquo;ll move the above guide to the main website eventually. I promise I&amp;rsquo;m not just funneling you over to Patreon where you can help support this bot.</description></item><item><title>Less used</title><link>https://sprintobot.com/docs/misc-sprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sprintobot.com/docs/misc-sprint/</guid><description>See also: Starting a sprint, and full list of Sprint commands.
Final #
/final Synonyms
@Sprinto#2517 final
@Sprinto#2517 words final
/words count: final Finalize your word count so Sprinto won&amp;rsquo;t wait for you to update it later. Can be used during a sprint or when time&amp;rsquo;s up and Sprinto is waiting for final word counts.
Final count #
/final count: count Finalize your word count with count words.
For example, to finalize with 1200 total words:</description></item></channel></rss>